Good Kill is a drama, thriller, war film directed by Andrew Niccol.
In the shadowy world of drone warfare, combat unfolds like a
video game–only with real lives at stake.
After six tours of duty, Air Force pilot Tom Egan now fights the
Taliban from an air-conditioned bunker in the Nevada desert.
But as he yearns to get back in the cockpit of a real plane and becomes increasingly troubled by the collateral damage he
causes each time he pushes a button, Egan’s nerves—and his relationship with his wife—begin to unravel.
Commandant Tom Egan, played by Ethan Hawke.
Molly Egan, played by January Jones.
Airman Vera Suarez, played by Zoë Kravitz.
M.I.C. Joseph Zimmer, played by Jake Abel.
Lieutenant Colonel Jack Johns, played by Bruce Greenwood.
Emily James, played by Alma Sisneros.
Good Kill is a 2014 American drama film written and directed by Andrew Niccol.
The film stars Ethan Hawke, Bruce Greenwood, Zoë
Kravitz, Jake Abel, and January Jones.
It competed for the Golden Lion at the 71st Venice International Film Festival.
It was also screened in the Special Presentations section of
the 2014 Toronto International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of suspicion, pilot,
drone, us military, air force base.
The tone is emotional and intense.